welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we'll be learning about the move
我们将在视频中了解这一举动
and also the crop tool so crop is a
还有裁剪工具 因此裁剪是一种
fancy word for cut it's the way that we
用花哨的词来形容削减这是我们的方式
would cut out a certain area like this
会像这样切出一块区域
and then it selects that we hit enter
然后它选择我们按Enter键
and now we've cut kind of the outside of
现在我们已经削减了一些外部的
our image away and then move as you know
我们的形象消失了 然后如你所知
is just going to move our image or we
是要改变我们的形象 还是我们
can move parts of the image as well so
也可以移动图像的某些部分 因此
we learn how to do that I do in control
我们学习如何做到这一点 我做的控制
Z to get this back to where it was
把它带回原来的位置
originally
原本
so let's slow down and go over these one
所以让我们放慢脚步 重温这一条
at a time let's do the crop first
现在让我们先收割庄稼
there's a couple ways to do crop when we
有几种方法可以做裁剪 当我们
select the crop tool it's shift to see
选择按住Shift键查看的裁剪工具
is the shortcut and the icon looks like
是快捷方式 图标看起来像
this and again these icons may be in a
这些图标一次又一次可能在
different location for you if you're
为您提供不同的位置
depending on how your dialog is sized
取决于对话框大小的大小
and also what version of you're
还有你是什么版本的
using the icons may even look different
使用图标甚至可能看起来不同
but find your crop tool and then to use
但找到您的裁剪工具 然后使用
it we just left-click and hold the mouse
如果我们只需左键点击并按住鼠标
down the left mouse button and when we
按下鼠标左键 当我们
unclick it shades out the area that will
取消单击它会使将显示的区域变暗
be cut out and it keeps highlighted the
被剪掉 它保持突出显示
area that is going to be remaining and
将保留的区域和
then we hit the enter key on our
然后我们按下了回车键
keyboard and it performs that cut if we
键盘和它执行剪切 如果我们
don't like it we can go control Z and
不喜欢的话我们可以去控制Z和
just go back and we can redraw or a
只要回去 我们就可以重新画或者
better way is to just use these handles
更好的方法是只使用这些手柄
here before we hit Enter we can use
在我们按回车键之前 我们可以使用
these handles to sort of fine-tune and
这些手柄可以微调和
really crop into the area that we want
真的闯入我们想要的地区
we can also click on the corners and
我们还可以单击角和
resize this is sort of similar to the
调整大小这有点类似于
way we drew selections where when we
我们选择的方式是什么时候我们
resize one corner is fixed and a
调整一个角的大小是固定的 并且
shortcut we didn't really go over is if
我们没有仔细研究过的捷径是
we hold down the ctrl key while we're in
我们在里面的时候按住了ctrl键
the selection resize mode we can resize
选择调整大小模式我们可以调整大小
from based off of the center so I'm
从中锋出发 所以我
holding down the ctrl key right now
现在按住Ctrl键
rather than having a fixed point also
而不是有一个固定点也
what you might try is holding down the
您可以尝试的是按住
shift key and that'll let us scale
Shift键 这将使我们可以扩展
uniformly so even if I come down here
一律如此 即使我来到这里
and try and go just over to the right
然后试着向右转
any distance I go horizontally will also
我水平走的任何距离也会
go vertically when the shift key is held
按住Shift键时垂直移动
while in this resize mode that make
当处于此调整大小模式时
sense I'm gonna hit enter to confirm
感觉我要按回车键确认
this crop the move tool we've used in
这将裁剪我们在中使用的移动工具
the past when the move tool selected
选择移动工具时的过去
it'll move either the layer we
它会移动我们的那一层
can also tell it to move the selection
也可以告诉它移动所选内容
or the path based on these different
或基于这些不同的路径
modes over here but make sure you're on
模式在这里 但请确保您已打开
this move by layer and then right now
这是一层一层的移动 然后现在
it's just picking the active layer so
它只是选择活动的层 所以
whatever layer I click on will move I
我点击的任何层都会移动
only have one layer right now but to
现在只有一层 但
illustrate is a little bit better let's
插图更好一点 让我们
bring in a new image and keep this one
带来一个新的形象 并保留这个
here so I'll go file open and I'll
在这里 我会打开文件 我会
select this image right here so now I
在这里选择此图像 这样现在我
have two different projects I can see up
我可以看到两个不同的项目
top here there's this one of me standing
上面有一张我站着的照片
in the snow this is actually my brother
在雪地里 这实际上是我的兄弟
here and so I can copy this image of my
在这里 我可以复制我的
brother by going to right click and edit
兄弟 点击鼠标右键编辑
and go to copy or I can press ctrl C on
然后转到复制 或者我可以按Ctrl C On
the keyboard and that's now copied to
键盘 现在复制到
the clipboard this image then I can go
剪贴板上有这张照片 我就可以走了
over to the other image and go control V
转到另一个图像并按下Ctrl V键
on my keyboard to paste it or I can
在我的键盘上粘贴 或者我可以
right click and go to edit and go to
右键单击并转至编辑 然后转至
paste and that will paste this image
粘贴 这将粘贴此图像
well now I can click on the move tool
现在我可以点击移动工具了
and I can move this image around it's
我可以移动这张图片 它是
actually a layer if you notice over here
实际上是一层如果你注意到这里
it's a floating selection it's a
这是一个浮动选择 它是一个
separate layer from this image so it's
从这张图像中分离出层 这样它就
kind of like there's two layers right
好像有两层对的东西
now we can do two things we can choose
现在我们可以做两件我们可以选择的事情
to merge this as part of this image and
将其合并为此图像的一部分 并
combine them into one layer to do that
将它们合并到一个层中即可完成此操作
we just right click over here and go to
我们只需右键单击此处并转到
anchor layer now it's anchored in there
锚层现在已经固定在那里了
and if we try to move it
如果我们试图移动它
it'll everything will move together any
它会把一切都放在一起
scaling or anything we apply is going to
伸缩或我们应用的任何东西都将
move all these together I can go ctrl Z
把所有这些放在一起 我可以按Ctrl Z键
and get back to that point before I did
在我之前回到这一点
the merge because we can also right
合并 因为我们还可以对
click and go to new layer and what that
单击并转到新图层 然后执行以下操作
does it puts this floating selection on
它会启用浮动选择吗
its own new layer now we have two layers
它自己的新层现在我们有两个层
we can click and see each one
我们可以点击并查看每一个
individually and this lets us be able to
这让我们能够
still move this around we can crop just
还是把它移来移去 我们只需
this image or just do either one of
此图像或仅执行以下任一操作
these images independently from the
这些图像独立于
other if we do the crop tool right now
如果我们现在使用裁剪工具
and we want to crop in just a part of
我们只想插手一部分
this image but keep everything out here
这张照片 但把所有东西都放在这里
unaffected we don't do it this way if we
不受影响我们不会这样做 如果我们
do it'll just crop in like this
做了它就会像这样突然出现
but I can go ctrl Z and before I select
但我可以按Ctrl Z键 在我选择
the crop notice there's some options
裁判员注意到有一些选择
under crop as well there's one called
在庄稼下也有一种叫
current
当前
lair only if I check that and then draw
只有在我检查后再画的情况下才能找到巢穴
my crop selection and then hit enter it
我的裁剪选择 然后按Enter
will only crop just the layer that I'm
只会裁剪我所在的那一层
working on does that make sense and so
这样做有意义吗？
if we didn't have that selected then it
如果我们没有选择它 那么它
would treat everything as one and crop
会把每件事都当做一个整体
all layers together there's also some
所有的层次加在一起也有一些
other options here and we'll play with
其他选项在这里 我们将尝试
more of these in the future we can silk
在未来 我们可以用丝绸制作更多这样的东西
we can instead of drawing this we could
我们可以不画这个 我们可以
draw and then we could fine tune it over
抽签 然后我们可以微调一下
here and change the size notice as I
在这里更改尺寸通知 因为我
click these it's moving subtly the size
点击这些 它微妙地移动着大小
of it and we can also use our scroll
我们也可以用我们的卷轴
wheel to change that as well there is
也有改变这一点的车轮
one more way to crop I want to show you
还有一种裁剪的方法 我想让你看看
and that is just by using the selection
这仅仅是通过使用选择
tool so we can select an area and it
工具 这样我们可以选择一个区域 然后它
looks similar to crop only notice when
在以下情况下看起来与裁剪相似
the selection tool is used it doesn't
选择工具已使用 而不是
everything else doesn't get grayed out
其他的一切都不会变灰
and if we hit enter
如果我们按回车键
it doesn't crop or do anything so the
它不会裁剪或做任何事情 所以
selection tool even though the interface
选择工具即使在界面上
sort of looks the same and we can resize
看起来差不多 我们可以调整大小
it it's not the crop tool so pay
如果不是裁剪工具 那就付钱吧
attention to that but what this will let
注意这一点 但这会让
us do is when we have a selection we can
我们所做的就是当我们有一个选择时 我们可以
crop to that selection all we have to do
裁剪到该选区 我们所要做的就是
is click on image and go to crop to
是点击图像并转到裁剪
selection and that will crop to whatever
选择 它将被裁剪成任何内容
we have selected we talked about that a
我们已经选择了 我们谈到了
little bit in the past like if we were
就像我们在过去
to do a circle selection and we want to
做一个圆圈选择 我们想
crop to a circle it'll still do it as a
剪成一个圆圈 它仍然会做
square we can go image crop to selection
正方形 我们可以选择图像裁剪
and that'll kind of crop that out so
这样就可以把它去掉了
some ways we'll learn how we could cut
我们将学习如何削减
out if we wanted to have transparency in
如果我们想在
the corners there but just know you can
但你要知道你可以
crop that way as well by cropping to
作物的方式 以及通过作物
whatever you have selected but it'll
无论你选择了什么 但它会
still always crop in a square or
仍然总是在一个正方形
rectangle well hopefully you found this
希望你能找到这个
informative go ahead and play with crop
信息继续前进 玩作物
and play with move and the next videos
玩move和接下来的视频
we're going to be doing some more of
我们会做更多的
this where we copy certain images and
我们复制某些图像
paste them we'll be playing with rotate
粘贴它们 我们将玩旋转
and shear and learning how to composite
剪切和学习如何合成
multiple images together appreciate you
多张图片一起欣赏你
watching leave your questions comments
观看留言留言
below and I'll catch you in the next
下面 我会在下一个赶上你
video
视频